Welcome to the Hospital Management System.
Viewing the dashboard with system statistics.
Navigating to the Departments page.
Viewing existing departments in the system.
Going to the Doctors section.
Adding a new doctor to the system.
Entering doctor information.
Selecting the Cardiology department.
Entering phone number.
Creating the doctor record.
Doctor successfully added to the system.
Navigating to the Patients page.
Adding a new patient.
Entering patient name and details.
Setting patient age to 35.
Entering contact information.
Creating the patient record.
Patient successfully registered.
Going to the Appointments section.
Booking a new appointment.
Selecting the doctor for the appointment.
Selecting the patient.
Setting the appointment date and time.
Entering the reason for visit.
Booking the appointment.
Appointment successfully created.
Returning to the dashboard.
Viewing updated system statistics.
Demo complete.