# Hospital Management System Demo Script
Welcome to the Hospital Management System demonstration.
This is a complete full-stack application built with Ruby on Rails and React.
Let's begin by exploring the dashboard.
Here we can see statistics for departments, doctors, patients, and appointments.
Now navigating to the Departments section.
Clicking Add Department to create a new department.
Entering the department name: Emergency Medicine.
Adding a description: 24/7 Emergency care services.
Clicking Create to save the department.
The new department has been successfully added to the system.
Now let's navigate to the Doctors section.
Clicking Add Doctor to register a new physician.
Entering the doctor's name: Dr. Jane Smith.
Selecting the department: Emergency Medicine.
Adding the phone number: 555-1234.
Clicking Create to save the doctor information.
Dr. Jane Smith has been successfully added to the system.
Next, let's navigate to the Patients section.
Clicking Add Patient to register a new patient.
Entering the patient name: John Doe.
Setting the age to 35 years.
Adding the contact number: 555-5678.
Clicking Create to save the patient record.
John Doe has been successfully registered in the system.
Now let's book an appointment.
Navigating to the Appointments section.
Clicking Book Appointment to create a new appointment.
Selecting the doctor: Dr. Jane Smith from Emergency Medicine.
Selecting the patient: John Doe.
Choosing the date and time for tomorrow.
Entering the reason: Routine checkup and consultation.
Clicking Book to confirm the appointment.
The appointment has been successfully scheduled.
Returning to the Dashboard to view updated statistics.
All statistics have been updated to reflect the new entries.
The demonstration is now complete.
Thank you for watching this Hospital Management System demonstration.