Viewing the dashboard
Navigating to Departments
Viewing existing departments
Going to Doctors section
Clicking Add Doctor
Entering doctor name
Selecting department
Entering phone number
Creating doctor record
Doctor added successfully
Navigating to Patients
Clicking Add Patient
Entering patient name
Setting patient age
Entering phone number
Creating patient record
Patient registered successfully
Going to Appointments
Clicking Book Appointment
Selecting doctor
Selecting patient
Setting appointment date
Entering visit reason
Booking appointment
Appointment created successfully
Returning to Dashboard
Viewing updated statistics
Demo complete